Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society ephemera collection ARC.272
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Downtown Brooklyn Development Association, undated (Drawer 7)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- The East (Drawer 7)
  Includes materials related to Uhuru Sasa School.
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Emerald Association of Long Island (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Energy Center (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Entertainment (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Flatbush Historical Society (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Fund for the Borough of Brooklyn (Drawer 8, Box 1)
- Organizations and Institutions -- Gravesend Historical Society (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Grow NYC, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Guardian Angels, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Hebrew Educational Society, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Historic Districts Council, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Independent Neighborhood Democrats, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Junior League of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Kings County Historical Society, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Long Island Association, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- National Maritime Historical Society, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Neighbors Together Corporation, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- New England Society of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Nurses Association of the Counties of Long Island, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Paragon Progressive Community Action, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Plymouth Institute, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Society of Colonial Wars, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Society of Old Brooklynites, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- United Boys Brigade of America (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- United Merchants of 5th Avenue, undated (Drawer 8)
- Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Visiting Nurse Association, undated (Drawer 8)
- Parks -- General, undated (Drawer 8)
- Parks -- Brooklyn Botanic Garden (Drawer 8, Box 2)
- Parks -- Brooklyn Bridge Park, undated (Drawer 8)
- Parks -- Fort Greene Park, undated (Drawer 8)
- Parks -- Grand Army Plaza, undated (Drawer 8)
- Parks -- Prospect Park (3 folders) (Drawer 8)
- Police -- Police Department, undated (Drawer 8)
- Politics, Government, Legal -- General (2 folders), undated (Drawer 8)
- Politics, Government, Legal -- Campaign Songs, undated (Drawer 8)
- Politics, Government, Legal -- Political Campaign Ephemera (2 folders) (Drawer 8)
- Politics, Government, Legal -- Republican Party Banquets, undated (Drawer 8)
- Population, undated (Drawer 8)
- Prison Ships, undated (Drawer 8)
- Prisons, undated (Drawer 8)
- Religion -- General, undated (Drawer 8)
- Religion -- Jehovah's Witnesses, undated (Drawer 8)
- Religion -- Synagogues, undated (Drawer 8)
- Religion -- Synagogues -- Congregation Beth Elohim, undated (Drawer 8)
- Religious Life and Customs (Drawer 8)
- Social Life, Lifestyle, Social Customs -- Bicycles, undated (Drawer 8)
- Social Life, Lifestyle, Social Customs -- General, undated (Drawer 8)
- Social Services, undated (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- General, undated (Drawer 8, Box 1)
- Sports -- Brooklyn Dodgers Football Team -- Programs and Newsletters, undated (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- Brooklyn Scorecard, undated (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- Brooklyn Sports Center (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- Brooklyn-Queens Marathon and Indoor Games, undated (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- Crescent Football Programs, undated (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- Horse Racing Programs, undated (Drawer 8)
- Sports -- Miscellaneous Tickets, News Clippings, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Atlantic Avenue, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Atlantic Avenue Tunnel, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Belt Parkway (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Bergen Street, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Brooklyn Queens Expressway, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Brooklyn Queens Greenway, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Flatbush Avenue, undated (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Street Names (Drawer 8)
- Streets -- Washington Avenue, undated (Drawer 8)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- General, undated (Drawer 8)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- The Athenaeum, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Brooklyn Academy of Music, undated (Drawer 9, Box 1)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Brooklyn Philharmonia, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Fox Theatre (Box 1)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Loew's Kings, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Loew's Oriental, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- The Majestic, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Montauk Theater, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- New Brighton Theater, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Payton's Theater, undated (Drawer 9)
- Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Tilyou Family, undated (Drawer 9)
- Tourism and City Guides -- Guidebooks, undated (Drawer 9)
- Tourism and City Guides -- Tourism Industry (Descriptions/Tours), undated (Drawer 9)
- Tourism and City Guides -- Walking Tours, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- General (2 folders) (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Brooklyn Elevated Railroad Company, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Brooklyn Rapid Transit Company, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit Company (BMT), undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Brooklyn Union Elevated Railroad Company, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Elevated Railways, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Ferries (2 folders) (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- L.I.R.R. (2 folders) (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Metropolitan Transit Authority (2 folders) (Drawer 9, Box 2)
- Transportation -- Miscellaneous (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- NYC Transit Authority, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Subways General, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Trains General, undated (Drawer 9)
- Transportation -- Trolleys, undated (Drawer 9, Box 1)
- Transportation -- Union Ferry of NY and Brooklyn Ferry Union, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Brooklyn Studies Seminars, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Central Brooklyn Model Cities, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Civil Improvement, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Gentrification, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Housing, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Public Housing, undated (Box 1)
- Urban Studies -- Urban Development, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Urban Planning, undated (Drawer 9)
- Urban Studies -- Urban Renewal, undated (Drawer 9)
- Waterfront, undated (Drawer 9)
- Women, undated (Drawer 9)
- World War I -- Postcards, undated (Drawer 9)
- World War II -- War Ration Books, undated (Drawer 9)